protecting your family is your number
one priority icic Lombard presents the
perfect plan for you the family Shield
plan is comprehensive flexible unique it
covers more to protect more some of the
key features of this plan are infectious
disease benefit personal accident
benefit
flexibility family policy discount
tenure and renewal discount the
Infectious Disease benefit can be very
helpful as various illnesses have become
more common now it provides for coverage
against specific Vector Bond diseases
rabies and tetus gastrointestinal
infections viral and nervous infections
personal accident benefit is a key
factor for protection it covers death
and disabilities adventure sports broken
bones and children's education grant
this plan offers you what you need you
can opt for any one or more base
benefits under one or more sections you
will be eligible for the base benefits
and or extensions if premium has been
paid once more multiple add-on covers to
choose from are available too this plan
offers you a tenure and renewal discount
too you can get a policy term of up to 3
years with long-term discount you also
get a 5% renewal discount the renewal
premium must be paid on or before the
policy expiry date or within 30 days
that's not all you get a family policy
discount of up to 7.5% too give your
family the protection they deserve and
give yourself a hassle-free claim
experience too with ICC Lombard's family
Shield plan you are our priority